Community standards for starters our
broker is as smart as he is courageous
aggressively growing his company when
others retreated is a masterful
motivator connecting with agents and
employees like few others can
our honoree is a wonderful teacher
helping people achieve far beyond their
personal expectations
Andy is a Relentless optimist seeing the
bright side and even the darkest of
situations
equally telling our honoree is
universally loved and respected by his
age so if one time producer his
leadership
attitude and friendship have changed my
life
is that another he has the vision for a
company and the heart for the agents
the third top producer
he is a mentor and leader I would follow
into any real estate battle
those are clearly some pretty big
statements
with his entire company marched into a
steady and positive beat it's no
surprise this organization constantly
achieves and dominates
2012 the company posted more than two
billion dollars in sales volume and 11
000 transaction signs it's a perennial
for Gibraltar historical member and one
of the industry's fastest growing real
estate brokerages
the company sells more listings at a
higher value than any other real estate
company in its Marketplace yet in the
middle of all of this Commerce the
company never loses sight of its mission
to help others and give back to the
community
through its support of both
a number of organizations including the
sunshine kids Foundation Toys for Tots
Opportunity Village and move for Hunger
big Talent
big passion Lasting Impressions on
people and community
ladies and gentlemen our provincial real
estate broker of the Year never has a
bad meeting
just about anyone's disposition with his
optimism and perspective
ladies and gentlemen our broker of the
year is
Mr Mark starter
I just want to really thank you I'm so
fortunate to be able to do what I do and
have the people that I do and be
surrounded with such professionals and
people who care and who are excited and
really I really really appreciate this
thank you so much